[
  {
    "question": "1 x 1 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      -33,
      55,
      38,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 2 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -35,
      -57,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 3 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      -64,
      3,
      -33,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 4 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      78,
      -36,
      4,
      66
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 5 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      5,
      3,
      0,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 6 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      29,
      73,
      6,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 7 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      -58,
      0,
      59,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 8 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      8,
      -26,
      36,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 x 9 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      -38,
      57,
      -35,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 1 =",
    "correct": 2,
    "choices": [
      55,
      -65,
      -22,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 2 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -21,
      55,
      -53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 3 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      -30,
      19,
      6,
      69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 4 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      -56,
      -51,
      8,
      -9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 5 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      11,
      -51,
      10,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 6 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      -31,
      -12,
      -32,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 7 =",
    "correct": 14,
    "choices": [
      -81,
      14,
      -65,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 8 =",
    "correct": 16,
    "choices": [
      16,
      -34,
      -45,
      46
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 9 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      72,
      -59,
      33,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 1 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      -63,
      -20,
      3,
      -30
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 2 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      2,
      6,
      37,
      -78
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 3 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      -53,
      9,
      -50,
      -27
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 4 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      33,
      -81,
      12,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 5 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      -2,
      15,
      -63,
      64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 6 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      13,
      18,
      68,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 7 =",
    "correct": 21,
    "choices": [
      21,
      -4,
      -37,
      53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 8 =",
    "correct": 24,
    "choices": [
      -20,
      24,
      54,
      33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 9 =",
    "correct": 27,
    "choices": [
      -64,
      27,
      -21,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 1 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -13,
      11,
      -64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 2 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      8,
      -67,
      0,
      -47
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 3 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      17,
      -7,
      -75
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 4 =",
    "correct": 16,
    "choices": [
      68,
      -74,
      16,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 5 =",
    "correct": 20,
    "choices": [
      20,
      40,
      66,
      -29
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 6 =",
    "correct": 24,
    "choices": [
      30,
      24,
      28,
      9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 7 =",
    "correct": 28,
    "choices": [
      -34,
      28,
      35,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 8 =",
    "correct": 32,
    "choices": [
      32,
      -8,
      81,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 9 =",
    "correct": 36,
    "choices": [
      5,
      36,
      -22,
      -53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 1 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      -48,
      5,
      40,
      -20
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 2 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      17,
      -8,
      10,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 3 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      15,
      -21,
      -66,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 4 =",
    "correct": 20,
    "choices": [
      6,
      -67,
      20,
      43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 5 =",
    "correct": 25,
    "choices": [
      25,
      1,
      60,
      -49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 6 =",
    "correct": 30,
    "choices": [
      -56,
      30,
      18,
      81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 7 =",
    "correct": 35,
    "choices": [
      55,
      35,
      14,
      -47
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 8 =",
    "correct": 40,
    "choices": [
      40,
      45,
      61,
      79
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 9 =",
    "correct": 45,
    "choices": [
      65,
      45,
      -24,
      -9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 1 =",
    "correct": 6,
    "choices": [
      -57,
      -37,
      6,
      -31
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 2 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      12,
      30,
      -31,
      -69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 3 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      54,
      17,
      72,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 4 =",
    "correct": 24,
    "choices": [
      -12,
      24,
      49,
      -34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 5 =",
    "correct": 30,
    "choices": [
      -47,
      -71,
      16,
      30
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 6 =",
    "correct": 36,
    "choices": [
      55,
      -28,
      36,
      77
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 7 =",
    "correct": 42,
    "choices": [
      -17,
      -43,
      29,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 8 =",
    "correct": 48,
    "choices": [
      48,
      -33,
      -28,
      -1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 9 =",
    "correct": 54,
    "choices": [
      25,
      54,
      -43,
      48
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 1 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      60,
      21,
      7,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 2 =",
    "correct": 14,
    "choices": [
      14,
      -68,
      -69,
      -75
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 3 =",
    "correct": 21,
    "choices": [
      -59,
      21,
      -50,
      76
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 4 =",
    "correct": 28,
    "choices": [
      62,
      33,
      28,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 5 =",
    "correct": 35,
    "choices": [
      -53,
      53,
      35,
      -52
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 6 =",
    "correct": 42,
    "choices": [
      67,
      -64,
      42,
      39
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 7 =",
    "correct": 49,
    "choices": [
      68,
      -43,
      11,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 8 =",
    "correct": 56,
    "choices": [
      56,
      31,
      -18,
      81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 9 =",
    "correct": 63,
    "choices": [
      23,
      63,
      -81,
      41
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 1 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      -71,
      8,
      49,
      -32
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 2 =",
    "correct": 16,
    "choices": [
      -10,
      -54,
      -42,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 3 =",
    "correct": 24,
    "choices": [
      -13,
      -51,
      24,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 4 =",
    "correct": 32,
    "choices": [
      65,
      32,
      -33,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 5 =",
    "correct": 40,
    "choices": [
      40,
      24,
      -58,
      13
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 6 =",
    "correct": 48,
    "choices": [
      -70,
      48,
      -47,
      -78
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 7 =",
    "correct": 56,
    "choices": [
      21,
      -58,
      44,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 8 =",
    "correct": 64,
    "choices": [
      64,
      49,
      30,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 9 =",
    "correct": 72,
    "choices": [
      -13,
      12,
      -33,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 1 =",
    "correct": 9,
    "choices": [
      49,
      -74,
      9,
      -29
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 2 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      -7,
      -33,
      -56,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 3 =",
    "correct": 27,
    "choices": [
      47,
      -6,
      74,
      27
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 4 =",
    "correct": 36,
    "choices": [
      -43,
      30,
      36,
      -64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 5 =",
    "correct": 45,
    "choices": [
      -12,
      45,
      -58,
      47
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 6 =",
    "correct": 54,
    "choices": [
      -19,
      54,
      66,
      -43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 7 =",
    "correct": 63,
    "choices": [
      63,
      -45,
      2,
      -60
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 8 =",
    "correct": 72,
    "choices": [
      69,
      58,
      -15,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 9 =",
    "correct": 81,
    "choices": [
      -61,
      -76,
      27,
      81
    ]
  }
]
